A Guide to the The Photographic Archive of Fairfax County, Virginia - The Slide Collection, 1961-1998
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- Reston, Lake Anne Village Center, 1968; Box 5: REST-13
- Reston, Lake Anne Village Center, 1968; Box 5: REST-14 (1 of 3)
- Reston, Lake Anne Village Center, 1968; Box 5: REST-14 (2 of 3)
- Reston, Lake Anne Village Center, 1968; Box 5: REST-14 (3 of 3)
- Reston, 1968; Box 5: REST-15
- Reston, 1968; Box 5: REST-16
- Reston, 1968; Box 5: REST-17
- Reston, 1968; Box 5: REST-18 (1 of 2)
- Reston, 1968; Box 5: REST-18 (2 of 2)
- Reston, 1968; Box 5: REST-19
- Reston, 1968; Box 5: REST-20
- Reston, 1968; Box 5: REST-21
- Reston, 1968; Box 5: REST-22
- Reston, 1970; Box 5: REST-24
- Reston, Lake Anne Village Center (photo by Phil Clark), 1968; Box 5: REST-25
- Reston (photo by Phil Clark), 1968; Box 5: REST-26
- Reston, Lake Anne Village Center (photo by Norman Klein, architect), 1968; Box 5: REST-27
- Reston, Lake Anne Village Center (photo by Norman Klein, architect), 1966; Box 5: REST-28
- Reston, Lake Anne Village Center (photo by Norman Klein, architect), 1966; Box 5: REST-29
- Reston, Lake Anne Village Center (photo by Norman Klein, architect), 1966; Box 5: REST-30
- Reston, Lake Anne Village Center (photo by Norman Klein, architect), 1966; Box 5: REST-31
- Reston, Lake Anne Village Center (photo by Norman Klein, architect), 1966; Box 5: REST-32
- Reston, Lake Anne Village Center (photo by Norman Klein, architect), 1966; Box 5: REST-33
- Reston, Lake Anne Village Center (photo by Norman Klein, architect), 1966; Box 5: REST-34
- Reston, Lake Anne Village Center (photo by Norman Klein, architect), 1966; Box 5: REST-35
- Reston, Lake Anne Village Center (photo by Norman Klein, architect), 1966; Box 5: REST-36
- Reston, Lake Anne Village Center (photo by Norman Klein, architect), 1966; Box 5: REST-37
- Reston, Lake Anne Village Center (photo by Norman Klein, architect), 1966; Box 5: REST-38
- Reston, Lake Anne Village Center (photo by Norman Klein, architect), 1966; Box 5: REST-39
- Reston, Lake Anne Village Center (photo by Norman Klein, architect), 1966; Box 5: REST-40
- Reston, Lake Anne Village Center (photo by Norman Klein, architect), 1966; Box 5: REST-41
- Reston, Lake Anne Village Center (photo by Norman Klein, architect), 1966; Box 5: REST-42
- Reston, Lake Anne Village Center (photo by Norman Klein, architect), 1966; Box 5: REST-43
- Reston, Lake Anne Village Center (photo by Norman Klein, architect), 1966; Box 5: REST-44
- Reston, Lake Anne Village Center (photo by Norman Klein, architect), 1966; Box 5: REST-45
- Reston, Lake Anne Village Center (photo by Norman Klein, architect), 1966; Box 5: REST-46
- Reston, Lake Anne Village Center (photo by Norman Klein, architect), 1966; Box 5: REST-47
- Reston, Lake Anne Village Center (photo by Norman Klein, architect), 1966; Box 5: REST-48
- Reston, Lake Anne Village Center (photo by Norman Klein, architect), 1966; Box 5: REST-49
- Reston, Lake Anne Village Center (photo by Norman Klein, architect), 1966; Box 5: REST-50
- Reston, Lake Anne Village Center (photo by Norman Klein, architect), 1966; Box 5: REST-51
- Reston, Lake Anne Village Center (photo by Norman Klein, architect), 1966; Box 5: REST-52
- Reston, Lake Anne Village Center (photo by Norman Klein, architect), 1966; Box 5: REST-53
- Reston, Lake Anne Village Center (photo by Norman Klein, architect), 1966; Box 5: REST-54
- Reston, Lake Anne Village Center (photo by Norman Klein, architect), 1966; Box 5: REST-55
- Reston, Lake Anne Village Center (photo by Norman Klein, architect), 1966; Box 5: REST-56
- Chain Bridge Road Historical Marker (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-1
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-2
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-3
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-4
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-5
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-6
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-7
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-8
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-9
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-10
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-11
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-12
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-13
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-14
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-15
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-16
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-17
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-18
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-19
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-20
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-21
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-22
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-23
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-24
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-25
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-26
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-27
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-28
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-29
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-30
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-31
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-32
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-33
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-34
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-35
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-36
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-37
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-38
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-39
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-40
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-41
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-42
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-43
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-44
- Freedom Hill Park, Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-45
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-46
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-47
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-48
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-49
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-50
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-51
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-52
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-53
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-54
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-55
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-56
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-57
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-58
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-59
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-60
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-61
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-62
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-63
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-64
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-65
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-66
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-67
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-68
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-69
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-70
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-71
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-72
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-73
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-74
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-75
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-76
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-77
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-78
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-79
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-80
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-81
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-82
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-83
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-84
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-85
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-86
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-87
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-88
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-89
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-90
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-91
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-92
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-93
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-94
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-95
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-96
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-97
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-98
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-99
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-100
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-101
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-102
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-103
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-104
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-105
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-106
- Remanent of historic road in the McLean, Great Falls, and Vienna areas (photo by Dr. Winslow Hatch), Undated; Box 5: ROADS-107
- Rolling Road Railroad Bridge, Burke, 1968; Box 5: ROLL-1
- Rolling Road Railroad Bridge, Burke, 1968; Box 5: ROLL-2
- Rolling Road Railroad Bridge, Burke, 1968; Box 5: ROLL-3
- Rolling Road Railroad Bridge, Burke, 1968; Box 5: ROLL-4
- Rolling Road Railroad Bridge, Burke, 1968; Box 5: ROLL-5
- St. John's Episcopal Church, Centreville (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 5: SAIN-J-1
- St. John's Episcopal Church, Centreville (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 5: SAIN-J-2
- St. John's Episcopal Church, Centreville (photo by E. Breitenbach), Undated; Box 5: SAIN-J-3
- St. Mary's Catholic Church, Fairfax Station (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 5: SAIN-M-1
- St. Mary's Catholic Church, Fairfax Station (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 5: SAIN-M-2
- Salona, McLean (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 5: SALO-1
- Salona, McLean (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 5: SALO-2
- Seven Corners, c. 1958 Aerial view of Route 50 and Route 7, Undated; Box 5: SEV-C1 (1 of 2)
- Seven Corners, c. 1958 Aerial view of Route 50 and Route 7, Undated; Box 5: SEV-C1 (2 of 2)
- Seven Corners Before Overpass in 1948 (photo by Quentin Porter), Undated; Box 5: SEVE-2
- Site of Shepherd's Ordinary and Wiley's Tavern site, approach to Difficult Run (photo by Nan Netherton), 1976 August; Box 5: SHEP-1
- Shiloh Baptist Church, 1972; Box 5: SHIL-1 (1 of 3)
- Shiloh Baptist Church, 1972; Box 5: SHIL-1 (2 of 3)
- Shiloh Baptist Church, 1972; Box 5: SHIL-1 (3 of 3)
- Shiloh Baptist Church, 1972; Box 5: SHIL-2 (1 of 3)
- Shiloh Baptist Church, 1972; Box 5: SHIL-2 (2 of 3)
- Shiloh Baptist Church, 1972; Box 5: SHIL-3 (3 of 3)
- "Shipwreck", Potomac River south of Hunting Creek (photo by Nan Netherton), 1973 April; Box 5: SHIP-1
- Spring Glade, 1972; Box 5: SPRI-G-1 (1 of 3)
- Spring Glade, 1972; Box 5: SPRI-G-1 (2 of 3)
- Spring Glade, 1972; Box 5: SPRI-G-1 (3 of 3)
- Spring Hill, McLean (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 5: SPRI-H-1
- Spring Hill, McLean (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 5: SPRI-H-2
- Spring Hill, McLean (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 5: SPRI-H-3
- Spring Hill, McLean, Oak Tree (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 5: SPRI-H-4
- Spring Hill, McLean, Oak Tree (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 5: SPRI-H-5
- Spring Hill, McLean, Oak Tree (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 5: SPRI-H-6
- Springfield Station in 1930 (photocopy by Jack L. Hiller), 1981; Box 5: SPRINGF-1
- Sugarland Run Cabin, 1968; Box 5: SUGA-1
- Sugarland Run Cabin, 1968; Box 5: SUGA-2
- Sugarland Run Cabin, 1968; Box 5: SUGA-3
- Sugarland Run Cabin, 1968; Box 5: SUGA-4
- Sugarland Run Cabin, 1968; Box 5: SUGA-5
- Sugarland Run Cabin, 1968; Box 5: SUGA-6
- Sugarland Run Cabin, 1968; Box 5: SUGA-7
- Sugarland Run Cabin, 1968; Box 5: SUGA-8
- Sugarland Run Cabin, 1968; Box 5: SUGA-9
- Sugarland Run Cabin, 1968; Box 5: SUGA-10
- Sugarland Run Cabin, 1968; Box 5: SUGA-11
- Sugarland Run Cabin, 1968; Box 5: SUGA-12
- Sugarland Run Quarry, 1968; Box 5: SUGA-13
- Sugarland Run Quarry, 1968; Box 5: SUGA-14
- Suglarland Run Road, 1968; Box 5: SUGA-15
- Suglarland Run Road, 1968; Box 5: SUGA-16
- Suglarland Run Road, 1968; Box 5: SUGA-17
- Suglarland Run Road, 1968; Box 5: SUGA-18
- Suglarland Run Road, Crossing of Sugarland Run, 1974; Box 5: SUGA-19
- Suglarland Run Road, Old bridge abutments next to Sugarland Run Ford (photo by Nan Netherton), 1974; Box 5: SUGA-20
- Suglarland Run Road, Ford (photo by Nan Netherton), 1974; Box 5: SUGA-21
- Sully, 1968; Box 5: SULL-1
- Sully, Rear view taken prior to removal of kitchen wing, 1974 May; Box 5: SULL-2 (1 of 3)
- Sully, Rear view taken prior to removal of kitchen wing, 1974 May; Box 5: SULL-2 (2 of 3)
- Sully, Rear view taken prior to removal of kitchen wing, 1974 May; Box 5: SULL-2 (3 of 3)
- Sully, 1968; Box 5: SULL-3
- Sully, 1968; Box 5: SULL-4
- Sully, Prior to restoration (photo by Richard Netherton), 1974; Box 5: SULL-5
- Sully, House and office building, 1972; Box 5: SULL-6
- Sully, Panorama from Route 28 (photo by Richard Netherton), 1974; Box 5: SULL-9 (1 of 2)
- Sully, Panorama from Route 28 (photo by Richard Netherton), 1974; Box 5: SULL-9 (2 of 2)
- Sully, Entrance, Undated; Box 5: SULL-10
- Sully, Stone Dairy being remodeled, 1972; Box 5: SULL-11 (1 of 3)
- Sully, Stone Dairy being remodeled, 1972; Box 5: SULL-11 (3 of 3)
- Sully, Stone Dairy, 1972; Box 5: SULL-12 (1 of 2)
- Sully, Stone Dairy, 1972; Box 5: SULL-12 (2 of 2)
- Sully, Schoolhouse, 1972; Box 5: SULL-13
- Sully, Office, 1968; Box 5: SULL-14
- Sully, Garden, Undated; Box 5: SULL-15 (1 of 2)
- Sully, Garden, Undated; Box 5: SULL-15 (2 of 2)
- Sully, Garden, 1974; Box 5: SULL-16
- Sully, Garden, 1968; Box 5: SULL-17
- Sully, Garden, 1974; Box 5: SULL-18
- Little Sully, Dead tree, Undated; Box 5: SULL-19
- Sully, Floral pattern, Undated; Box 5: SULL-20
- Sully, Reenactors in costume, 1968 June; Box 5: SULL-21
- Sunset Hills, House, Undated; Box 5: SUNH-1
- Sunset Hills, Warehouse, Undated; Box 5: SUNH-2
- Sunset Hills, Gazebo, 1972; Box 5: SUNH-3 (1 of 2)
- Sunset Hills, Gazebo, 1972; Box 5: SUNH-3 (2 of 2)
- Swinks Mill Miller's House, 1965; Box 5: SWINKS-1
- Swinks Mill Barn, 1965; Box 5: SWINKS-2
- Swinks Mill Miller's House, 1969; Box 5: SWINKS-3
- Swinks Mill Miller's House, 1969; Box 5: SWINKS-4
- Swinks Mill Barn and Carport, 1969; Box 5: SWINKS-5
- Swinks Mill Miller's House and Barn, 1969; Box 5: SWINKS-6
- Swinks Mill Miller's House and Studio, 1969; Box 5: SWINKS-7
- Swinks Mill Miller's House and Barn, 1969; Box 5: SWINKS-8
- Swinks Mill Miller's House, 1973; Box 5: SWINKS-9
- Swinks Mill Miller's House, 1973; Box 5: SWINKS-10
- Swinks Mill Miller's House, 1973; Box 5: SWINKS-11
- Swinks Mill Miller's House, 1973; Box 5: SWINKS-12
- Tobacco Cultivation (engraving), Undated; Box 5: TOBA-1 (1 of 2)
- Tobacco Cultivation (engraving), Undated; Box 5: TOBA-1 (2 of 2)
- Tobacco Warehouse (etching by William Newman, 1800), Undated; Box 5: TOBA-3
- Cartouche from map of Virginia and Maryland by Joshua Fry and Pete Jefferson, 1775, Undated; Box 5: TOBA-4
- Tobacco Warehouse, Danville, VA, Undated; Box 5: TOBA-5 (1 of 2)
- Tobacco Warehouse, Danville, VA, Undated; Box 5: TOBA-5 (2 of 2)
- Tobacco Hogshead on a Rolling Road, Undated; Box 5: TOBA-6
- Towlston Grange (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1966; Box 5: TOWL-1
- Towlston Grange (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1966; Box 5: TOWL-2
- Towlston Grange (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1966; Box 5: TOWL-3
- Towlston Grange (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1966; Box 5: TOWL-4
- Kalorama Springs (Tricketts), Colvin Run, 1972; Box 5: TRIC-1 (1 of 2)
- Kalorama Springs (Tricketts), Colvin Run, 1972; Box 5: TRIC-1 (2 of 2)